How big do you
think is the risk
of a backlash against
AI that will somehow
kind cause governments to
do what from your
perspective might be stupid
things Because I'm just
thinking back to the
era of globalization in
the 1990s when there
was indeed some displacement
of governments didn't do
enough The public backlash
was such that we've
up sort where we
are now Do you
think that there is
a risk that there
will be a growing
antipathy towards what you
are doing and your
companies in the kind
body politic I think
there's definitely a I
think that's kind of
There's fear and there's
about these things like
jobs and livelihoods I
think there's a of
that I it's going
to be very complicated
the next few years
I think geopolitically but
also the various factors
here Like we want
to and we're trying
to do this with
AlphaFold and our science
work and Isomorphic our
spin out company solve
all diseases
come up with new
energy sources I think
as a it's clear
we'd want that